There are about 19 companies which can
remain in focus in the market today.  News has been seen in these.
GMR Airports' post-market
update is that the company
reported a 0.9% year-on-year growth in passenger traffic to around 32 million in the fourth quarter of FY24.
In this, domestic traffic
was 2 crore 41 lakh and international
traffic was 77 lakh.  The
update in Aurobindo Pharma is that the company's subsidiary,
Trainim Biologics Pvt Ltd, has
extended its existing contract with Mark Sharp Domain Singapore Trading Pvt Ltd for manufacturing operations.   The
update in SDB Financials is that the
company has
registered a 41% year-on-year growth in profit after tax i.e. PAT for the month ended March 31, 2026.  The
company's PAT was Rs 751 crore, which is
higher than the same quarter last year.   The
company's PAT was Rs 531 crore in the same quarter last year.  The update in ICICI LBD is
that the company has released its results
for the quarter and its rate has
shown a growth of 7.025% year-on-year.
547 crores has been reported by the company.
In the same quarter last year, it had come to Rs 510 crore.
You will also have to keep an eye on fertilizer companies
because
due to the conflict going on in West Asia, the supply
is low.  Meanwhile, the prices of urea have
reached record highs.   It has
almost doubled.  The news of India's high-
rate tender could set a new
benchmark.  Considering the
shortage of supply and the demand due to the coming monsoon,
prices may increase.   The
update on Brigade Enterprises Limited is
that the
company has
signed a joint venture agreement for 8.63 acres of land in Gujur, East Bengaluru.  Will pave the way for a
large integrated residential township project.
A residential
project township will be developed on this.
Talking about the GHB Infra project, the
update is that the company has received orders
for road construction and some other civil works in Maharashtra.
This contract is worth Rs 815 crore.  The
company has received this order from APCO Infratech Private Limited.
Talking about Concor i.e. Container Corporation of India Limited, the company has manufactured nine
BLSS i.e. Spine Car Brakes
and has given a contract of Rs
175 crore to Brake Weight & Co Limited for its supply.
So this important
update has been seen in it.  The
update in RBCON Research Ltd is that the company has
bought stake in Arena Life Science for around Rs 175 crore and this is 85% of the
stake bought.
It has entered the Indian central nervous system formulation market.  The
update on Samee Hotels is that
the company, through its subsidiary Samee Skyland Pvt Ltd, has signed
a lease agreement for a 162-room hotel project in Noida.   The
update at all cargo terminals is that
its volume is continuously increasing.
Quarterly earnings were also strong due to robust operations and higher throughput.  The
update on Lakshya Power Tech is
that the company has received an order worth ₹641 crore from
Nidanata Limited for operation and maintenance of care assets at the firm.  The
update in Retail Corporation of India is that the
company has
received a Letter of Intent of Rs 100 crore from the Divisional Commissioner in Konkan Division for maintenance of an IT solution.  That means the company has been
seen getting an order worth Rs 100 crore.  The
update in GTPL Hathway is that the
company has released its quarterly results
and the company has seen a net loss of Rs 15 crore.
Last year, PAT worth Rs 10 crore was seen.
Whereas the company's revenue has increased by 4%.   It has been Rs
923 crore.  Despite this, the company's
PAT has gone into negative.  The
update in Tejas Network is that on April 15, the
company has informed about its bad report.  The
company has said that
due to a huge decline in its revenue, the
company's loss has reached Rs 211 crore.
Last year the loss was Rs 71 crore.
However, the company's order book has
increased by 49% at the annual level.  It has become Rs 1514
crore.  Nexus Fund has sold its stake worth Rs
186 crore in Delivery through a block deal.
And
if there has been anyone who has been the main buyer of this stake, it has been Morgan
Stanley.  The update at John Crockrell India is
that the company has
received an order worth Rs 300 crore from GSW Steel for a galvanizing line at its Khopoli plant.   The
update on Suraj Estate Developers Ltd is
that the company has announced the acquisition of a land parcel in Dadar West, Mumbai at a
cost of around ₹18 crore.
So these have been
important updates.  I hope
you liked our video.   Don't
forget to tell me how you liked it.  Also
subscribe to our channel.
Press the bell icon.